import { Question } from "../../interfaces/question";

export const questionsTypeScriptSsetOne: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript is a statically typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript is a server-side programming language developed by Microsoft.",
    answerTwo:
      "TypeScript is a CSS preprocessor used for styling web applications.",
    answerThree:
      "TypeScript is a database management system for SQL databases.",
    answerFour:
      "TypeScript is a testing framework used for unit testing JavaScript code.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What are the key features of TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Key features of TypeScript include static typing, classes, interfaces, and support for modern JavaScript features.",
    answerOne:
      "Key features of TypeScript include dynamic typing, prototypes, and global variables.",
    answerTwo:
      "Key features of TypeScript include built-in form validation, server-side rendering, and routing.",
    answerThree:
      "Key features of TypeScript include automatic memory management, garbage collection, and exception handling.",
    answerFour:
      "Key features of TypeScript include built-in animation effects, DOM manipulation, and event handling.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What is the difference between TypeScript and JavaScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript is a statically typed language, while JavaScript is dynamically typed.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript is a compiled language, while JavaScript is interpreted.",
    answerTwo:
      "TypeScript is only used for backend development, while JavaScript is used for both frontend and backend.",
    answerThree:
      "TypeScript supports classes and interfaces, while JavaScript uses prototypes and objects.",
    answerFour: "TypeScript has stricter syntax rules compared to JavaScript.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What are the benefits of using TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Benefits of using TypeScript include improved code maintainability, enhanced developer productivity, and early error detection.",
    answerOne:
      "Benefits of using TypeScript include faster runtime performance compared to JavaScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "Benefits of using TypeScript include seamless integration with popular frameworks like React and Angular.",
    answerThree:
      "Benefits of using TypeScript include built-in data persistence and database management.",
    answerFour:
      "Benefits of using TypeScript include automatic code generation and documentation.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "How does TypeScript help with scalability in large codebases?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript helps with scalability by providing type checking, interfaces, and better tooling support for refactoring.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript offers built-in load balancing and distributed computing capabilities for large-scale applications.",
    answerTwo:
      "TypeScript includes advanced code optimization techniques to improve performance in large codebases.",
    answerThree:
      "TypeScript enables automatic code generation for creating boilerplate code in large projects.",
    answerFour:
      "TypeScript provides seamless integration with cloud platforms for scalable deployment.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is type annotation in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Type annotation allows explicit declaration of a variable's type.",
    answerOne:
      "Type annotation is a way to check runtime errors in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Type annotation is a way to optimize TypeScript code.",
    answerThree: "Type annotation is TypeScript's garbage collection system.",
    answerFour:
      "Type annotation allows explicit declaration of a variable's type.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is a tuple in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Tuple is a TypeScript type allowing array with fixed types of elements.",
    answerOne: "Tuple is a TypeScript object with key-value pairs.",
    answerTwo: "Tuple is a function type in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Tuple is a class in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Tuple is a TypeScript type allowing array with fixed types of elements.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is an interface in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Interface in TypeScript is used for type checking, especially for complex structures.",
    answerOne: "Interface in TypeScript is used for handling exceptions.",
    answerTwo: "Interface in TypeScript is a type for high order functions.",
    answerThree: "Interface in TypeScript is a feature for defining constants.",
    answerFour:
      "Interface in TypeScript is used for type checking, especially for complex structures.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How is 'any' type used in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer: "'any' type allows a variable to be of any type in TypeScript.",
    answerOne: "'any' type in TypeScript is used to declare constants.",
    answerTwo: "'any' type is TypeScript's feature for exception handling.",
    answerThree: "'any' type in TypeScript is used for garbage collection.",
    answerFour: "'any' type allows a variable to be of any type in TypeScript.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What is the role of '.tsconfig' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'.tsconfig' in TypeScript is used for project configuration settings.",
    answerOne: "'.tsconfig' in TypeScript is used for dependency management.",
    answerTwo: "'.tsconfig' in TypeScript is used for error handling.",
    answerThree:
      "'.tsconfig' in TypeScript is used for database connection settings.",
    answerFour:
      "'.tsconfig' in TypeScript is used for project configuration settings.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What are generics in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Generics provide a way to make components work with any data type.",
    answerOne: "Generics are TypeScript's built-in data types.",
    answerTwo: "Generics are a type of error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Generics are TypeScript's syntax for creating new classes.",
    answerFour:
      "Generics provide a way to make components work with any data type.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "How are namespaces used in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Namespaces are used to group related code and prevent global scope pollution.",
    answerOne: "Namespaces are used for memory management in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Namespaces are used to handle exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Namespaces are used to declare constants in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Namespaces are used to group related code and prevent global scope pollution.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What are decorators in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Decorators provide a way to add annotations or modify classes and class members.",
    answerOne: "Decorators are used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "Decorators are TypeScript's syntax for defining new data types.",
    answerThree: "Decorators are used for memory management in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Decorators provide a way to add annotations or modify classes and class members.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What is 'never' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'never' type represents the type of values that never occur, such as a function's return value that always throws an exception.",
    answerOne:
      "'never' type is used to represent undefined values in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'never' type is used to represent null values in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "'never' type is used to represent any type of values in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'never' type represents the type of values that never occur, such as a function's return value that always throws an exception.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "How does TypeScript handle null and undefined?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript has specific types for null and undefined and can enforce their checks with strict null checking.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript uses exception handling to manage null and undefined.",
    answerTwo: "TypeScript treats null and undefined as 'any' type.",
    answerThree: "TypeScript converts null and undefined into empty strings.",
    answerFour:
      "TypeScript has specific types for null and undefined and can enforce their checks with strict null checking.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What is 'any' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer: "'any' type is a dynamic type that can hold any value type.",
    answerOne: "'any' type represents null or undefined values.",
    answerTwo: "'any' type is a type that never holds a value.",
    answerThree: "'any' type is a special function type in TypeScript.",
    answerFour: "'any' type is a dynamic type that can hold any value type.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "What does the 'readonly' modifier do in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'readonly' modifier makes a property as read-only in the class.",
    answerOne: "'readonly' modifier allows a class property to be reassigned.",
    answerTwo: "'readonly' modifier makes a class property private.",
    answerThree: "'readonly' modifier makes a class property write-only.",
    answerFour:
      "'readonly' modifier makes a property as read-only in the class.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What are Tuple types in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Tuple types allow you to express an array with a fixed number of elements whose types are known.",
    answerOne: "Tuple types are dynamic data types that can hold any value.",
    answerTwo: "Tuple types are immutable data types in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Tuple types are used to represent function types.",
    answerFour:
      "Tuple types allow you to express an array with a fixed number of elements whose types are known.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What is 'type inference' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Type inference is TypeScript's ability to figure out the type of a variable on its own.",
    answerOne:
      "Type inference refers to the ability to change a variable's type.",
    answerTwo:
      "Type inference refers to TypeScript's exception handling mechanism.",
    answerThree: "Type inference is a tool for debugging TypeScript code.",
    answerFour:
      "Type inference is TypeScript's ability to figure out the type of a variable on its own.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What are union types in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer: "Union types allow variables to hold values of multiple types.",
    answerOne: "Union types are used to represent null or undefined values.",
    answerTwo: "Union types are complex data types in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Union types represent collections of similar data types.",
    answerFour: "Union types allow variables to hold values of multiple types.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "What is an Enum in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Enum is a special type used to define a collection of related values that can be numeric or string values.",
    answerOne: "Enum is a type used to handle exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "Enum is a type used to represent null or undefined values in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "Enum is a type used to define private variables in TypeScript classes.",
    answerFour:
      "Enum is a special type used to define a collection of related values that can be numeric or string values.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "What is the 'unknown' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'unknown' is a type-safe counterpart of 'any'. Anything is assignable to 'unknown', but 'unknown' is not assignable to anything but itself and 'any' without a type assertion or a control flow based narrowing.",
    answerOne: "'unknown' type represents a function that never returns.",
    answerTwo:
      "'unknown' type represents a variable that can only be null or undefined.",
    answerThree:
      "'unknown' type is a type used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'unknown' is a type-safe counterpart of 'any'. Anything is assignable to 'unknown', but 'unknown' is not assignable to anything but itself and 'any' without a type assertion or a control flow based narrowing.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "What is 'type alias' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Type aliases allow you to create a new name for a type. It can represent a primitive, union type, tuple, or any other type that you'd want to re-use.",
    answerOne:
      "Type aliases are used to declare global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Type aliases are used to represent constants in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Type aliases are used to handle exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Type aliases allow you to create a new name for a type. It can represent a primitive, union type, tuple, or any other type that you'd want to re-use.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "What are type guards in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Type guards are expressions that perform runtime checks that guarantee the type in a certain scope.",
    answerOne:
      "Type guards are used to declare global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Type guards are used to represent constants in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "Type guards are special types used for defining private variables.",
    answerFour:
      "Type guards are expressions that perform runtime checks that guarantee the type in a certain scope.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "What is a 'type assertion' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Type assertion is like a type cast in other languages, but it doesn't perform any special checking or restructuring of data. It has no runtime impact and is used purely by the compiler.",
    answerOne: "Type assertion is TypeScript's way of handling exceptions.",
    answerTwo:
      "Type assertion is used to define global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "Type assertion is a type that represents a function that never returns.",
    answerFour:
      "Type assertion is like a type cast in other languages, but it doesn't perform any special checking or restructuring of data. It has no runtime impact and is used purely by the compiler.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "What is the 'as' syntax in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "The 'as' syntax is used for type casting, allowing you to tell the compiler to treat an object as a different type.",
    answerOne: "'as' syntax is used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'as' syntax is used to declare global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "'as' syntax is used to define functions in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "The 'as' syntax is used for type casting, allowing you to tell the compiler to treat an object as a different type.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "What are optional parameters in TypeScript functions?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Optional parameters are parameters that a function can be called without. They are denoted by a '?' at the end of the parameter name.",
    answerOne:
      "Optional parameters are always the first parameters in a function.",
    answerTwo: "Optional parameters are parameters that cannot be undefined.",
    answerThree: "Optional parameters are parameters that must be objects.",
    answerFour:
      "Optional parameters are parameters that a function can be called without. They are denoted by a '?' at the end of the parameter name.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "What is the 'this' keyword in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "The 'this' keyword refers to the object instance on which a method is currently being called, similar to its use in JavaScript.",
    answerOne: "'this' keyword is used to handle exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "'this' keyword is used to declare global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "'this' keyword is used to define constants in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "The 'this' keyword refers to the object instance on which a method is currently being called, similar to its use in JavaScript.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "What is a 'type predicate' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'type predicate' is a function that returns a boolean and has a special return type that asserts the type in the positive case.",
    answerOne: "A 'type predicate' is a type that can only be true or false.",
    answerTwo:
      "A 'type predicate' is a type that represents a function that never returns.",
    answerThree:
      "A 'type predicate' is a type that can only be null or undefined.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'type predicate' is a function that returns a boolean and has a special return type that asserts the type in the positive case.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "What are 'mapped types' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Mapped types allow you to create new types based on old ones by transforming properties.",
    answerOne: "Mapped types are used to handle exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "Mapped types are used to declare global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "Mapped types are used to represent constants in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Mapped types allow you to create new types based on old ones by transforming properties.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "How does TypeScript support OOP features?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript supports OOP features by providing classes, interfaces, and inheritance.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript supports OOP by translating OOP code to procedural code.",
    answerTwo:
      "TypeScript supports OOP by providing automatic garbage collection.",
    answerThree:
      "TypeScript supports OOP by providing features like tuples and enums.",
    answerFour:
      "TypeScript supports OOP features by providing classes, interfaces, and inheritance.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "What is a 'symbol' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'symbol' is a primitive type unique and immutable data type introduced in ES6, and is also available in TypeScript.",
    answerOne: "A 'symbol' is a global variable in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "A 'symbol' is a collection of related constants in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "A 'symbol' is a type that never holds a value in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'symbol' is a primitive type unique and immutable data type introduced in ES6, and is also available in TypeScript.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "What does 'strict mode' do in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'Strict mode' enforces stronger type-checking in your TypeScript code to avoid potential runtime errors.",
    answerOne: "'Strict mode' enables garbage collection in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "'Strict mode' optimizes TypeScript code for better performance.",
    answerThree:
      "'Strict mode' is used to enable distributed computing in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'Strict mode' enforces stronger type-checking in your TypeScript code to avoid potential runtime errors.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "What are intersection types in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Intersection types allow you to combine multiple types into one, enabling objects to have properties of several types.",
    answerOne:
      "Intersection types are used to represent null or undefined values in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Intersection types are types that can only hold numbers.",
    answerThree:
      "Intersection types are the types that always throw an exception.",
    answerFour:
      "Intersection types allow you to combine multiple types into one, enabling objects to have properties of several types.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: "What does the 'partial' utility type do in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'Partial' utility type makes all properties of a given type optional.",
    answerOne: "'Partial' type is used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'Partial' type is used to represent constants in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "'Partial' type is used to represent undefined or null values in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'Partial' utility type makes all properties of a given type optional.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "What is the 'never' data type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'Never' is a type that represents the type of values that never occur, such as a function that always throws an exception.",
    answerOne: "'Never' is a type for nullable variables in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'Never' is a special type for constant values.",
    answerThree: "'Never' is a data type for boolean values.",
    answerFour:
      "'Never' is a type that represents the type of values that never occur, such as a function that always throws an exception.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "How does TypeScript handle asynchronous operations?",
    goodAnswer:
      "TypeScript supports asynchronous operations through the use of Promises and async/await syntax.",
    answerOne:
      "TypeScript handles asynchronous operations using a special type of loop.",
    answerTwo: "TypeScript doesn't support asynchronous operations.",
    answerThree:
      "TypeScript handles asynchronous operations using special type annotations.",
    answerFour:
      "TypeScript supports asynchronous operations through the use of Promises and async/await syntax.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "What is the purpose of a 'namespace' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'namespace' in TypeScript is used to group logically related code. This is primarily used to organize code in a large-scale application.",
    answerOne:
      "A 'namespace' is used to declare variables that can be used globally throughout a TypeScript application.",
    answerTwo: "A 'namespace' is used to define a special type of object.",
    answerThree: "A 'namespace' is a kind of function in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'namespace' in TypeScript is used to group logically related code. This is primarily used to organize code in a large-scale application.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "What is a 'tuple' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'tuple' is a TypeScript type that allows you to express an array where the type of a fixed number of elements is known, but not necessarily the same.",
    answerOne:
      "A 'tuple' is a kind of function that can be used to encapsulate related code.",
    answerTwo:
      "A 'tuple' is a TypeScript type that represents a list of items of the same type.",
    answerThree: "A 'tuple' is a constant type in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'tuple' is a TypeScript type that allows you to express an array where the type of a fixed number of elements is known, but not necessarily the same.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: "What is a 'type guard' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'type guard' is a syntax you can use to check the type of a variable within a block of code.",
    answerOne:
      "A 'type guard' is a special type that only accepts numeric values.",
    answerTwo:
      "A 'type guard' is a syntax for defining global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "A 'type guard' is a method to handle errors in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'type guard' is a syntax you can use to check the type of a variable within a block of code.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "What is a decorator in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A decorator is a special kind of declaration that can be attached to a class declaration, method, accessor, property, or parameter in TypeScript.",
    answerOne: "A decorator is used to define global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "A decorator represents a constant value in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "A decorator is a tool for handling exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A decorator is a special kind of declaration that can be attached to a class declaration, method, accessor, property, or parameter in TypeScript.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "What is a namespace in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A namespace is used in TypeScript to group related code. This helps avoid collisions between different code segments or libraries that might have the same names for functions, classes, or variables.",
    answerOne: "A namespace is a tool for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "A namespace represents a constant value in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "A namespace is used to define private variables in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A namespace is used in TypeScript to group related code. This helps avoid collisions between different code segments or libraries that might have the same names for functions, classes, or variables.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "What is a module in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A module in TypeScript is a way to contain related code. This can include variables, functions, classes, interfaces, etc.",
    answerOne: "A module is a way to define global variables in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "A module is a tool for handling exceptions in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "A module represents a constant value in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "A module in TypeScript is a way to contain related code. This can include variables, functions, classes, interfaces, etc.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "What is the 'void' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'void' in TypeScript is a type with no values. It is usually used to indicate that a function does not return any value.",
    answerOne: "'void' is a type used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "'void' is a type that represents a function that never returns.",
    answerThree: "'void' is a type used to represent null or undefined values.",
    answerFour:
      "'void' in TypeScript is a type with no values. It is usually used to indicate that a function does not return any value.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: "What is the 'null' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'null' in TypeScript is a special type that only contains the value null. It is usually used to indicate that a variable should not have a value.",
    answerOne: "'null' is a type used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo:
      "'null' is a type that represents a function that never returns.",
    answerThree: "'null' is a type used to represent any data type.",
    answerFour:
      "'null' in TypeScript is a special type that only contains the value null. It is usually used",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "What is a Tuple in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "Tuple in TypeScript is an array where type of a fixed number of elements is known.",
    answerOne: "Tuple is a technique for handling errors in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "Tuple is a function in TypeScript.",
    answerThree:
      "Tuple is a data type representing undefined values in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "Tuple in TypeScript is an array where type of a fixed number of elements is known.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "What is 'any' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'any' type in TypeScript allows any type of value, bypassing type-checking.",
    answerOne: "'any' type is a null value in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'any' type is a function in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "'any' type is used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'any' type in TypeScript allows any type of value, bypassing type-checking.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "What is 'never' type in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "'never' type in TypeScript represents the type of values that never occur.",
    answerOne: "'never' type is a null value in TypeScript.",
    answerTwo: "'never' type is a function in TypeScript.",
    answerThree: "'never' type is used for error handling in TypeScript.",
    answerFour:
      "'never' type in TypeScript represents the type of values that never occur.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "What is a 'generic' in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "A 'generic' in TypeScript allows you to create reusable components that can work with a variety of types.",
    answerOne:
      "A 'generic' in TypeScript is a special type that can only hold numeric values.",
    answerTwo:
      "A 'generic' in TypeScript is used for error handling in asynchronous operations.",
    answerThree:
      "A 'generic' in TypeScript is a syntax for defining global variables.",
    answerFour:
      "A 'generic' in TypeScript allows you to create reusable components that can work with a variety of types.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "What is the 'keyof' operator in TypeScript?",
    goodAnswer:
      "The 'keyof' operator in TypeScript is used to create a union type of all property names of a given object type.",
    answerOne:
      "The 'keyof' operator in TypeScript is used to define constant values.",
    answerTwo:
      "The 'keyof' operator in TypeScript is a special type that can only hold boolean values.",
    answerThree:
      "The 'keyof' operator in TypeScript is a syntax for handling exceptions.",
    answerFour:
      "The 'keyof' operator in TypeScript is used to create a union type of all property names of a given object type.",
    isAnswerCorrect: false,
  },
];
